cellulardeals.com 2008-09-14

# Privacy Policy - Protecting Your Privacy and Security - Simplexity

* * *

## We Take Your Privacy Seriously

### **Simply put, we promise that:

• We will only ask for personal information required to complete your order.  
• We will use security safeguards such as SSL encryption to protect your information.  
• We will never use your personal information for the purpose of spam.

**

## Protecting Your Privacy and Security

  * What Information We Collect and How We Use It
  * Location Information
  * Personally Identifiable Information
  * Forward-To-A-Friend and Refer-A-Friend
  * Supplementation of Information
  * Sharing of Your Information
  * Sharing of Affiliate Information in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process
  * Third Party Sharing of Information
  * Live Help Function
  * Other Non-Personally Identifiable Information
  * Legal Process/Disclaimer
  * Choices/Opt Out
  * Cookies
  * Tracking Pixels
  * Links
  * Security
  * Reviewing Your Information
  * Contact Us
  * Updates and Notification of Changes
  * Yahoo Privacy Policy

We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and exceeding our own internal standards and best practices. 

The CellularDeals.com store is operated by Simplexity, LLC. (“Simplexity”). We provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our site. This privacy statement covers the site www.cellulardeals.com .

Simplexity is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program and is authorized to use the TRUSTe trustmark. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity by promoting the use of fair information practices. To demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance with TRUSTe’s established privacy principles and comply with ongoing TRUSTe oversight.

By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, Simplexity has agreed to notify you of:  
• What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site   
• How the information is used   
• With whom the information may be shared   
• What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information   
• What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Simplexity control.   
• How you can correct or update your information.   

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or complaints arising from our use of your personal information, please contact our Customer Service Department via certified mail to Simplexity, 11130 Sunrise Valley Drive, Suite 300, Reston, VA 20191, or via e-mail at privacypolicy@simplexity.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process ([www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php)). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Simplexity to resolve your concerns.

## What Information We Collect and How We Use It

## Location Information

We collect location information in order to improve your shopping experience. If you shop for location-specific products such as a wireless rate plan, we ask for a zip code and record this information via a cookie so that we may display only services which are available in your area. We also save this information so that we don’t have to ask for it again on your next visit.

Information from IP addresses is used to help administer our Web site, to examine overall traffic trends, and to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

## Personally Identifiable Information

When you place an order for products or services we collect certain types of personally identifiable information required to fulfill those products or services, including (1) contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number); (2) payment information (such as credit card number); and/or (3) ID verification information (such as credit card number, date of birth, Social Security Number, or Driver's License Number).

We only collect ID verification information if it is required by a wireless carrier to process your application. For those customers applying for a new wireless service account, we submit your data into the wireless carrier's system so that the carrier may perform a standard industry credit check. Aside from approval status information, we do not have access to an applicant's credit-history information.

If you would like to place an order but are reluctant to provide this information online, you may provide it to us by telephone during normal business hours. Telephone agents are available when the Order By Phone button is visible on one of the shopping pages of our site. Simply click on this button to speak to an agent and provide your information over the phone.

We use the contact information you provide to communicate with you, such as to send you order confirmations, respond to your inquiries, provide you with important product update, warranty, or safety information. In addition, we use contact information you provide to offer you additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you, including newsletters from wireoffers.com, an affiliated site. You can easily opt out of a newsletter by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of these e-mails. We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes, unless you authorize us to do so.

## Forward-To-A-Friend and Refer-A-Friend

If you choose to use our email forwarding functionality or our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend the forwarded email or a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site, as applicable. We store this information for the sole purpose of forwarding the email or sending the one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at newsletter@simplexity.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

## Supplementation of Information

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our strategic partners, wireless providers, or the United States Postal Service) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

## Sharing of Your Information

Please be assured that any third parties who have access to the contact information you provide, including our subsidiary site, agents, contractors and business affiliates have agreed to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this privacy policy.

To fulfill your requests for products and services, we may need to share some of your personally identifiable information with the wireless provider from which you have requested service. More specifically, when you place an order for a new wireless account, we will share contact and ID verification information required by the wireless carrier to provide you with its services. The wireless provider may use this information for credit approval, service activation, and from time to time, for its own marketing purposes. You should consult the wireless providers' respective privacy policies, as this Notice does not cover their use of your information. Also, your shipping information will be shared with a shipping company such as FedEx, for the purposes of delivering your order.

We work closely with trusted third party business affiliates to provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you. We may share the contact information you provide with trusted third parties for the purposes of analyzing it to make your customer experience better or for offering products and services to you. In addition, you can access Simplexity through many third-party co-branded Web sites. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by Simplexity," you are on a co-branded page. Whenever you provide contact information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third-party site through which you access Simplexity. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as this Notice does not cover their use of your information.

## Sharing of Affiliate Information in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process

Information submitted by potential Affiliates in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process is submitted to Linkshare. Linkshare's privacy policy can be found at [www.linkshare.com.](http://www.linkshare.com/)

## Third Party Sharing of Information

Simplexity sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions, affiliations, sponsorships) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity.

## Live Help Function

To better serve you and respond to your questions regarding our products or services, we also maintain a Live Help function through which we can respond, in real time, to your questions about our products and services. This information enables us to understand the types of questions our users have about our products and services so that we may continue to improve our content and offerings.

## Other Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our service pages and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze service usage.

## Legal Process/Disclaimer

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request.

## Choices/Opt Out

If you prefer not to receive marketing information, including emails, from us, or wish to fully deactivate your account information from our records if you are no longer an active customer, simply let us know by sending a letter via certified mail to Simplexity, LLC, c/o Privacy Opt Out, 11130 Sunrise Valley Drive, Suite 300, Reston, VA 20191 or via e-mail to privacypolicy@simplexity.com Please note that even if you choose to opt out of marketing programs, if you are an active customer we will continue to send you important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information) which is not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

## Cookies

Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites.

In addition, some of our business affiliates (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies and their use is not covered by this privacy policy.

## Tracking Pixels

This site makes use of a technology designed to enhance your browsing experience. The technology makes use of a small and transparent Java applet to provide you with a faster browsing experience. In addition, aggregate reporting information is collected and made available to the site owner only. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used for this process.

## Links

This site may contain links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Our privacy policy does not cover these third parties' use of information. Visitors should consult the other companies' and sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

## Security

We have put in place multiple levels of physical and electronic security to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. These measures include secure web pages, VeriSign SSL certificate ensuring the privacy and security of order information, and HackerSafe certification, representing the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government and all major credit card providers.

All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet.

## Reviewing Your Information

If you would like to review and update or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, or if you no longer wish to continue your service with us, simply send your request via certified mail to Simplexity, LLC, 11130 Sunrise Valley Drive, Suite 300, Reston, VA 20191. You may also send your request via the Customer Support feedback section in our [Customer Support](http://www.whereismyorder.com/). To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us via the Customer Support feedback section in our [Customer Support](http://www.whereismyorder.com/).

## Updates and Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## Yahoo Privacy Policy

Simplexity, LLC works with Yahoo! to research certain web site usage and activities on our behalf. Yahoo! uses cookies, Web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies (collectively, “Beacons”) to conduct this research. The information collected through these Beacons is used to find out more about our users, including user demographics and usage patterns, for more accurate reporting and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. Information recorded through the use of these Beacons is aggregated and then shared with us. No personally identifiable information about you is shared by Yahoo! with Simplexity, LLC as a result of this research. If you prefer that Yahoo! not record information by means of these Beacons on the Simplexity, LLC. web site, visit Yahoo! at [http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/beacons/details.html to opt out.](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/beacons/details.html)

By visiting this web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

### **Last Updated January 2008**

---|---|---
